## OLIVER WOODWARD

Self-motivated Web Developer with comprehensive experience managing multiple clients. Passionate and hardworking to deliver on deadlines. Strong HTML and CSS programmer. Gifted Web Developer with broad and creative portfolio. Completes lucrative and labour-intensive projects. Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with calm and focused demeanor.

# I AM A HARD-WORKING INDIVIDUAL, WHO STRIVES FOR PERFECTION AND IS IN THE CONSTANT PURSUIT OF FURTHERING SELF.

a lust for life, is keen to learn and is a team player.

### CONTACT

EMAIL:

<u>oliverwoodward1@gmail.com</u> <u>07851260802</u>

<u>e-portfolio:</u>
<a href="https://orwportfolio.netlify.app/">https://orwportfolio.netlify.app/</a>

### **EDUCATION**

### **Leeds Beckett University**

1/09/2019 - 2022

After achieving 12 GCSEs ranging from A\*-B, and achieving 3 A levels (Bio, Chem and Physics) all at Bs, I applied for Biomedical Science at LBU.

I have been at Leeds Beckett University for 3 academic (currently in Thrid year) years now. In my time I have enjoyed learning various skills and techniques in the labs. I am a hard-working individual and keeping to a strict deadline is in my nature.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **KFC Staff Member**

2018-2021

I enjoyed the fast-paced environment of working in the food industry. I was trained to do everything there is to do, the only other people who are trained to do everything are the managers, this demonstrates I have an aptitude for quick learning, and I am a trustworthy individual as I counted and reported the cash intake of the tills.

## Ward Befriending Scheme

2018-2019

I spent a full year going to the wards helping elderly patients. This included talking to them, making them feel at ease, bringing their food and drink to them and creating a calm and relaxed environment. I went every weekend and on Wednesdays. This helped me gain valuable attributes pertaining to people and team skills.

### Royal Mail - Mail Sorter

2021-Present

Royal Mail is a great workplace for individuals who have a high work ethic, it involves a lot of manual intensive labour, which I don't shy away from, I get on and help out others whenever. I am usually given responsibilities usually reserved for high up individuals, but I have created strong trusting working relationships with my managers which enables me to take on further responsibilities.

### **SKILLS**

- Website optimisation
- UX/UI design
- Agile methodologies
- GitHub
- Front and back end development
- CSS
- Angular
- Customer service
- Web development projects